Then you tell you too much, that is, you can't tell
anything about what is happening in the book or exactly what is happening
Without you have to tell you a little
you have to give a tastes, a feeling
Small clues
You need to suggest
what the book is all about in an approximately
So that I can think: Yes, this sounds interesting, this is a
story I am interested in
This is a topic or theme that interests me
So one can generally talk about theme
Then you think the reader is not aware
The author since before
But is it a famous writer then maybe it's better to
say a little about how this one
the book, the new book is relate to
Books and styles
As this writer has written before
and then you have to
have some control over that writer but that
may be of interest to the reader that now has
the writer it and it suddenly wrote